RESUME

NUNSINEE VIKEN

Web Portfolio

https://www.webbymim.com/
https://webportfolio-2.vercel.app/

Contact

Address:

Haugeveien 9B, Bergen, Norway

Phone:

+47 484 60007

Email:

nunsinee@gmail.com

Hard & Soft Skills

Languages: HTML, JavaScript CSS, SASS, Styled-Component TypeScript, Web Responsive

Libraries: React

Framework: Next.js, Bootstrap,

React-Bootstrap

Testing: Jest

CMS: WordPress, Strapi

Design: Adobe XD, Adobe

Photoshop, and Adobe Illustrator

Database: MySQL

CI/CD: Git

Languages

English – C1 Norwegian – B1

Thai - C3

Summary

Front-end Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, WordPress, React, Bootstrap, Next.js, and Typescript. Strong background in Hospitality industry and customer services.

Education

Front-end Web developer- 2020-2022 NOROFF School, Norway

Master of Business Administration: Computer

Business- 2013

Ramkhamhaeng University, Thailand

Bachelor of Business Administration: Computer

Business- 2003

Prince of Songkhla University, Thailand

Experience

Reservation Manager: 2013-2014

Centara Grand Beach Resort & Spa, Thailand

Tour Manager: 2011-2013

Andaman trips and services travel agency, Krabi,

Thailand

Online tour manager & webmaster: 2009-2011 Andaman Web Holdings Co, Ltd, Krabi, Thailand

Webmaster: 2005-2009

Foundation for Community Educational Media -

Prachatai.comBangkok, Thailand